Let it shine.
This little light of mine.
Sammy!
Ruth.
No.
Come on, son.
It's okay.
My son has felt the call of sin.
You see what that gets you?
But the good Lord calls upon us to be
fishers of men who sin.
And shows them the way.
I
want you to swear to me
and the fourth congregation
to leave those sinning
ways where they lie.
I want you to promise right now.
Drop the guitar, Sammy.
In the name of God.
Let it go, Sammy.
Put it down.
Good morning, Miss Beatrice.
Did you storm in that gateside tonight?
You gonna tell me what
you're playing or am I
gonna have to hear it
through the grapevine?
You have a good one, Beatrice.
I'll see you at service tomorrow morning.
Morning, Ma.
Morning, baby.
Don't put that on your body, Sammy.
It'll dry you out.
I'm gonna put this on while it's still
wet.
Boy, you ain't got the sense God gave a
goose.
Hey, Mama said get up.
You Hogwood?
You boys twins?
Nah, we cousins.
That's good.
There she is.
He moved a ton of timber a month back in
his heyday.
Workers lived upstairs.
Y'all wash these floors?
Yeah.
What was on them?
I thought y'all was dead set on buying the
place.
The more time I spend with y'all, the less
sure I am you boys are serious about it.
Ain't no boys here.
I just grown me.
Who grown me in money and grown me in
bullets.
I didn't mean nothing by it.
Just the way we talk down here.
We'll take it.
The mill, the equipment, and the land that
it's standing on.
Damn.
Now understand, it's the last diamond you
ever gonna see from us.
And if we see you or any one of your Klan
buddies cross our property line,
we gonna kill them right where they stand.
Klan don't exist no more.
Okay then.
All right.
Say, what do you fellas plan on doing with
the place?
Morning, Pop.
You know, Pop, we're early, son.
Like you say, jump on the work.
Don't let the work jump on you.
Finish my quota for the day.
Yeah, I brought it in here.
I want you to help me with my sermon
tomorrow.
First Corinthians 10, 13.
Read.
No temptation has overtaken you except
what is common to mankind.
God is faithful.
He will not let you be tempted beyond what
you can bear.
But when you're tempted, he will also
provide a way out so that you can endure it.
Now, Pop, if you don't mind, I'm gonna be
late.
Late for what, boy?
Where you gotta be that's more important
than being in the house of God?
I've been working all week, Pop.
I'm gonna be free of all this for a day.
I'll be back in town for service in the
morning.
Son?
You keep dancing with the devil.
One day he's gonna follow you home.
Little cousin, come on out.
Got two dollars waiting on dime.
Sammy.
Oh, don't you worry now, Uncle Jack.
Gonna get them back to you in one piece.
Boy, look at you, all grown up.
Why are you big?
Daddy doing right by you?
So you're not putting his hands on you?
Nah, man.
Nothing too much.
What about them loved ones?
Only when they deserve it.
My mom usually hands out the whoopings.
Good.
Well, Uncle Jack always been good.
Yeah.
So tell me about Chicago.
I heard they ain't got Jim Thorpe there.
Black man can go where he want.
Boy, you can't be believing anything that
you hear.
Time to fill your head up with this
make-believe.
Me and your cousin?
We gonna give it to you straight.
Chicago ain't shit but Mississippi with
tall buildings instead of plantation.
That's why we came back here.
Figured we might as well deal with the
devil we know.
Well, who gonna watch the truck when I'm
in there talking to the childs?
Nigga, just let them see it's you.
We been gone a long time, Stack.
Seven years ain't long enough to forget
about us.
Don't move.
How about you leave that truck to us?
Watch this fool make sure he don't get in
no trouble.
You big enough to take me now,
huh?
I'll do what I can.
No, you'll do what you told.
We got 24 hours to turn this booze into
cash.
You keep your eyes open for anybody
staring too long.
This nigga don't know how to watch his own
back.
Last time you cleaned this?
Shit.
Last time I had to use it?
Cracker showing up late already got us
behind schedule.
Smoke.
Look at that sky.
That's a mighty fine day to be free,
ain't it?
I own Juke Joint.
Just like we always wanted.
Love you.
Love you too.
Be careful.
I will.
You with me.
You not little Lisa, is you?
Guilty as charged.
You daddy here?
Daddy?
What?
Old child.
Damn cat dragged in.
Who's your brother?
All right, listen.
Every cool's got a button on, towards the
top.
Anything you want to keep along,
you find it, lick that.
Not too hard.
Not too soft either.
This the hard or?
Too damn fast.
Why, you want to drive?
Come on, you don't want to drive.
On the way back.
All right, all right.
Come on, tell me.
You and Uncle Jerry, y'all doing okay?
You always said you would tell me what
happened to Uncle Adam when I got older.
Y'all ready to kill him?
Nah, we ain't killing him.
Smoke did.
Come
on.
Kill him!
That's my finger.
Man, just get your own damn thing.
Fuck you gone, nigga.
Bet this bull to beat you there.
Oh, you shot me.
Motherfucker.
Smoke.
Terry?
Boy, how you been?
I was doing better before you shot me in
the ass.
Why in the hell you trying to boost my
truck?
It's your truck.
I swear, Smoke.
Bullshit.
I told you it was his.
Wait, wait, Smoke.
I thought she was lying.
Y'all was supposed to be in Chicago
working for Capone.
Yeah, we back now.
Who he?
Just some nigga I met last week.
Where he from?
Maybell.
Can't have some nigga
from the Maybell plantation
talking about how he
almost robbed the twins.
Not without a limp to show for it.
Well, who gonna patch me up?
I ain't got no money.
What if I get sepsis or some shit now?
Y'all scoot on out the street.
Put some pressure on.
Get up, boy.
Our daddy knocked me unconscious.
By the time I came to, Smoke was halfway
done burning.
You used to beat y'all?
Me most of them.
He ain't mean it.
See, he been taking good care of that
thing.
Hey, I can't thank y'all enough for this.
I mean, it plays so right.
Yeah, that's, uh...
Charlie Patton's guitar.
Me and my brother won it off him in the
car game.
Hold on a sec.
You mean to tell me I had Charlie Patton's
guitar this whole time?
Swift old guy in your head.
Nah.
Now let's see if you can play like it.
Right here?
Yeah, right now.
Come on.
Watch this.
Travelin'
Travelin' She sure don't feel like that We
gon' make some money.
We gon' make some money.
Yo, take off.
Mama, daddy wants you.
Thank you.
Thanks, twin.
Oh, is that Delta Slim?
You know, there's two men out there.
Look like they been shot.
That be my doing.
I done already gave both of them money to
get them patched up.
Why you gotta come here bringin' trouble?
Trouble ain't all he bringin'.
Yeah, thank you for your generosity.
I guess that Chicago wind blew your black
asses back down there, huh?
You a boy?
That's my little cousin.
Preacher Boy Sam.
Happens to be the finest blues player in
all of Delta.
I got socks on this here, boy.
What the hell?
He know about the blues.
I can show you better than I can tell you.
Hold up now.
Hold up, hold up now.
This here my patch right here.
Now you wasn't his cousin.
And a young pup to boot.
I'll cut your ass too thin to fry.
Then you threaten him again, I'm gonna
make your drunk ass swat out of harmonica.
How you paying for this?
And he wants you to make a sign for him.
Rust job.
Gonna cost you.
I'm listening.
Twenty.
Fifteen for the front door sign and five
for the menu.
Ten.
Seven for the front door sign,
three for the menu.
Sixteen.
Fifteen.
Done.
Oh, we only got one color, by the way.
What color you got?
Red.
Fourteen.
Fourteen fifty.
With all these flowers right here.
And we got a deal.
Done.
I'll give you twenty dollars to come play
at our juke tonight.
I ain't never heard of your juke.
I've been to Messy's every Saturday night
for the last ten years.
Messy's gonna be there another ten years
after that, at least.
Shit.
There's probably more time than I got left
on this earth stack.
I play, and I get as much corn liquor as I
can drink.
Sending like me, I can't ask for more than
that.
Well, Slim, I'll drink to that.
Ooh.
What you got there, boy?
Oh, this?
It's an Irish beer.
Straight from the north side of Chicago.
Oh.
You say that's beer.
Wind ain't bring us down here empty
handed.
Nothing.
Goodness.
I got five hundred more bottles,
just like that.
Ice cold.
These two gonna be playing down at the old
sawmill.
You know the one.
The one on the riverbank right outside
Clarksdale.
Yeah, yeah.
We gonna have us a battle of the blues.
Y'all ready to eat?
Yeah.
Y'all ready to drink?
Y'all ready to sweat on this thing.
You gonna get funky like a Mississippi
donkey, y'all.
All right.
Get a drink on the twins when you get
there.
Where you get that one from?
I seen you somewhere before.
Maybe.
Same, don't you?
Time to time.
I'm a preacher, boy.
Curling.
I'm married, by the way.
Careful, boy.
You gonna bite off more than you can chew.
Maybe I'll see you tonight.
She's a white woman staring at you.
Shit.
You sure she white?
She walking over here right now.
Excuse me, boy.
Is this here smoke?
Or is this stack?
Don't look at her.
Just over there and keep playing.
Yeah, that's okay.
You know I waited for you.
I don't know how in the hell you gonna do
that.
Because you told me you loved me.
Well, I told you to
stay the fuck away from
me too, but I guess
you didn't hear that part.
Oh, I heard you.
I heard you loud and clear,
but then you stuck your tongue in
my coos and fucked me so hard
I figured you changed your mind.
Keep your voice down now, Mary.
It's not exactly how I remember it.
Oh, it ain't.
Remember falling asleep with your head on
my chest?
Leaving in the middle of the night without
a fucking word?
Or a note?
The hell are you doing back here?
I buried my mama yesterday, Stack.
Figured I might see you in smoke there as
much as she looked after you both.
But I guess y'all love lasted as long as y
'all could get something out of her.
You right.
That's all she was.
A fool?
Or one big?
Rot in hell, Stack.
Shit, I will.
Save your trifling ass a room.
Right next to me.
Shit.
Hey, Stack.
Who?
Maybe Shane won.
Boys get to getting.
Come on, Slam.
They take us to this big house full of
white folks.
Pass around right here and have us to
play.
See these white folks we were playing for?
They had real money.
Had y'all playing them old ragtime songs?
Y'all sure was.
We playing a fair amount of blues,
too.
Them Pecklewoods was nodding their heads,
stomping their feet.
Some of them was almost on the rhythm,
Stack.
And then Rice made we change it up.
Confusing.
See white folks, they like the blues just
fine.
They just don't like the people who make
it.
What's that got to do with the money?
I don't know.
I drank it.
Rice said he was going to
take that money and going
out to Little Rock to
start him a little church.
Did he?
That's a damn fool.
He took out all his money to pay for it.
Two dollar train ticket.
Train conductor saw him.
Clank got a hold to him.
Searched his pockets to find all that
money.
Met up a story about him.
Killing some white man for it and raping
that white man's wife.
And they lynched him right there in the
railroad station.
You know they cut off the man's room.
Mmm.
Come
on now, y'all got that guitar in your
hand, don't you boy?
Mmm.
Papa's here.
How you been?
No misery is worth complaining about.
You come along?
Yeah.
Stack on the other side of town.
What you come back for?
We bought that old sawmill.
Yeah.
We gonna patch it up.
Make it into a juke joint.
A juke joint?
That's one of Stack's ideas?
Yeah.
He figure tonight gonna be a grand
opening.
We got word they gonna make booze legal
again.
Figure that's our last chance to go legit.
I thought y'all was done with the Delta.
Last I heard, y'all were northern men.
Nah, we through with Chicago.
Chicago through with y'all?
What you asking?
Who you and Stack
robbed to get enough money
for them crackers to
sell you a whole meal.
Just this, Miss Annie.
And a pinch of hydrogen.
Alright.
Right.
Now, don't sell none of this on the way
home.
I don't want your momma coming at me crazy
later.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
I can't believe you taking this
make-believe shit.
Smoke, give me my money before I cut your
black ass.
You gonna put that blade up on me?
I'll trade you.
I don't want your money.
Don't be stupid now.
I ain't stupid.
Your money come with blood.
All money come with blood, baby.
Not like yours.
This shit won't even spin nowhere else.
I ain't going nowhere else.
I don't need that cursed money you got.
Ships.
Train.
I seen men die ways I didn't even know was
possible.
I ain't never saw no roots.
No demons.
No ghosts.
No magic.
Just power.
And only money.
I can give you that.
You fool.
All that war and whatever the hells you
been doing in Chicago.
And you back here in front of me.
Two arms, two legs, two eyes and a brain
that work.
How you know I ain't pray?
I work every root my grandmama taught me to
keep you and that crazy brother yours safe.
Every day since you been gone.
So all those roots ain't work on our baby?
I don't know.
But they work for you.
You still got that mojo bag.
That's you.
Why are you here Smoke?
We was hoping to serve food to Juke
tonight...
we want you to cook for us.
Elijah..
You gonna make me say it?
It still hurts coming back here,
but I love you, and I miss you.
Hey, Conebred!
Ooh, Stack?
Boy, a long time no see.
This here my wife, Therese.
Nice to meet you, Therese.
Likewise.
Need you to give us a moment.
Men got business to discuss.
No, uh-uh.
I ain't got time for your scheming,
Stack.
Behind on my quota.
Man, fuck your quota.
This is my wife right here, now.
I'm gonna need you to show some respect.
Yeah, well, fuck your wife, too.
What's that?
I said she was really gonna let you fuck
her when she found out how much money you
were about to get from this job I'm
offering.
And none of that nice and slow shit she
probably giving you now.
Shit, she might even let you put your peck
in her mouth.
Ooh.
Well, you should've stayed gone, because
I'm about to beat the black off of you.
Come on, come on, now!
Hey!
Well, how much money you talking about
paying him?
Oh, that's a good woman.
Come on.
We'll be back.
My uncle taught the word.
You tell me, boy, you swimming in a sea of
temptation.
But he don't know.
Same spirit flowed through those church
folk.
Flown through us, but this your blues.
It's flown a different way.
More honestly, you ask me.
It wasn't forced on us, like that
religion.
No, son.
We brought this with us, my home.
From the Delta?
Africa, preacher boy.
It's magic what we do.
It's sacred.
It'll be.
That dude, you gonna be ready?
I'm always ready, Slim.
Yeah, yeah, I gotta help.
I thought I could trust them, but they,
they tried to kill me.
Slow down.
Who's trying to kill you?
Choctaw.
Aw.
Sure wasn't just some fair-skinned
niggers.
Ain't no Indians around here for miles.
Oh, God.
Oh, they took my wife.
Oh, my God.
I'm a coward, ain't I?
I... I got gold.
Them dirty Indians meant to rob me.
They ain't get all of it.
Y'all can have it.
Just, just, just don't let them hurt me no
more.
Come on.
Ah, God bless you.
Put him in the nursery.
Evening, ma'am.
We're in pursuit of someone very
dangerous.
He might have come onto your property.
Have you seen anyone recently?
No.
Bert!
Is he in there with you, ma'am?
He's not what he seems.
God forbid you let him into your home.
And if so, we need to act now.
Killia!
Pushpa!
Chee-haw-ya.
Chee-ah-pah-san.
Eh-yah.
Chickie.
Indians came and went.
Bert!
Ah, he's just resting.
Yeah.
Mm, don't cry.
He's all better now.
Hey, baby.
Ah!
Right this way, babies.
Come on in.
Welcome to Club Juke.
You ought to get it poppin' like fish
greens, boy.
A little pause... and we are back.
Good evening.
You look mighty nice.
Thank you.
You made it.
This ain't no house party.
And it damn sure ain't no charity.
We taking cash.
U.S.
motherfucking dollars.
This ain't Chicago smoke.
The fuck that mean?
That old nigga worked his ass off for them
with the nickels.
See, these niggas been working in the
field all day.
When they show up here, let them enjoy
themselves.
They gotta feel wanted if you want us here
to work.
This place supposed to feel like it's for
them.
Right this way.
Uh-huh.
Uh, excuse me, ma'am.
You show you at the right place?
That's a damn good question, cornbread.
Little Mary?
Not so little no more, huh?
Little Mary.
Oh.
When you was selling
ass out in Little Rock, you
ever let a John pay with a
goddamn promissory note?
Hell no.
But, see, I wasn't selling ass in the
Delta.
You gon' play?
You gon' sign?
We'll see where the night takes us.
Your husband coming?
He's older.
Oh, hold on.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I don't think you should be here,
you see.
I'm with the twins.
With the twins?
Boy, if you don't get the fuck out in my
face.
I am with them, ma'am.
We met earlier at the train station.
I'm their little cousin.
Little cousin?
I think you should leave before they see
you.
Wait, you're not little Sammy.
The guitar.
You're old enough to drink now.
Come on, let me buy you a drink.
I don't know who do, and I can't talk
slick, but I know business.
And this is bad for business.
It's opening night.
Besides, there's gonna be a few of them
like this.
Please.
I need a goddamn cigarette.
Coming right up.
So you play that guitar that left you?
Yeah.
That's good.
You making any money with that thing?
Not really.
Not yet.
At least.
I tell you it didn't matter as long as you
love it, but that'll be horseshit advice.
What are you?
What am I?
I'm a human being.
Ah, that ain't what I meant.
I meant, you know, more
like... I know what you meant.
My mama's daddy was half black.
He raised her to keep the clan from
killing him.
You know my mama delivered the twins.
Really?
To save Stack life after he got stuck in
the mall.
And after she died, my mama nursed them
like they was her own.
And they had enough money to buy this
whole mill.
And they ain't even sent flowers to a
funeral.
Who sent your mama flowers?
Plenty of them.
Or why, she still a lot of smell?
Smell.
Am I right?
Let's go check in on Slim.
See if he don't need backup.
Take care of her all week.
No, no, I'm gonna handle it.
I got it.
I ain't going.
Come on.
Let's go.
I'm not here for you.
Then why you here then?
I come to hear the blues.
No, no.
They play the blues just fine in Arkansas.
Come on.
Home run.
Let's get out of the car.
Put your guns off me.
What's it gonna take?
Hm?
How much did it get you to get the fuck
on?
You can't pay me off.
Fine.
I'll pay one of these field bitches that
ain't here to drag your ass out then.
Shit.
You taught me how to fight.
I beat up every bitch in here and you know
it.
I taught you how to walk away when the
money's up too.
Got you a rich white husband.
Got you a farm.
Now go home to it.
I ain't ask for none of that.
All that shit was your idea.
I didn't want no white man.
I didn't want to be white.
I wanted to be with you.
You know I ain't shit.
Maybe I ain't shit neither.
All they take is the wrong
person in here to see you before
they get back to them crackers
and they gonna try to kill you.
What it matter to you?
Somebody out there hurt you.
Me and my brother gonna come kill them
all.
I was young enough to believe you were
coming back.
I waited.
I waited a long time.
But I'm grown now.
See?
You never planned to stay.
And I know you never planned to stay.
Why can't you just say that?
Say what?
That I love you.
That
I think about you every day.
I just wanted to keep you someplace safe.
And I was never gonna be here.
Beth.
I see y'all.
Hey.
I've been hearing about this one
particular young man all day.
He supposed to be a bad blues man.
Where you at, boy?
Where you at?
Come over here, man.
That's my little cousin, y'all.
Watch this.
Hold up.
Tell me who you are.
Where you from?
Yeah.
I'm Sammy Moore.
I'm a sharecropper from Sunflower
Plantation.
Oh, my God.
They call me Preacher Boy, on account of
my daddy being a pastor.
Amen.
I wrote this song for him.
Oh, my God.
Something I've been wanting to tell you
for a long time.
It might hurt you.
Hope you don't lose your mind.
Well, I was just a boy.
About eight years old.
Threw me a Bible.
On that Mississippi road.
See, I love you, Papa.
You did all you could do.
And they say the truth hurts.
So I lied to you.
Yes, I lied to you.
I love you.
Somebody tell me.
Somebody take me in your arms tonight.
All right.
Yeah.
Somebody take me in your arms tonight.
The sacred help be.
They got us trapped here, Preacher Boy.
But this is music.
We escape.
We backwards to ancestors.
Somebody take me.
We march forward to all that was yet to
come.
Somebody take me.
It's magic what we do.
Now, it's doubt time.
Stand at all, cause what I'm out here
doing You didn't preach at all See I'm
full of the blues, holy water too I know
the truth hurts, so I lied to you So
preach on, speak your words I know the
truth hurts, yes I lied to you But with
this here ritual We bring my heart right
here with us right now
Will somebody take me
We heal our people And we be free
Put your foot on that at least
I wanna try something Wait,
preacher boy In the law shop
first, locked here You're
beautiful I just wanna taste you
Shit Excuse me, how y'all doing?
Good?
Got enough drink?
Alright then.
Smoke one, two.
Got my little cousin
He call himself telling me about the
cotton I said shit That boy don't know
nothing Get the twins Come on,
get them
I tallied the till Aim What's the count?
Now that top figure That's
plantation money That bottom
figure That's real dollars
So what's the projection?
Two months And we out of fresh cash Hey
there Good evening How may I help you folks?
Oh, we heard tale of a party Drink,
food, lose music and the like You did?
We like to drink We happen to be musicians
and we walked here So, we hungry as dogs
Woof, woof You wouldn't mind us coming in
now, would you?
I think y'all in the wrong place What
makes you say that?
You fellas must be the owners of this
establishment That's right And you are?
Name's Ramek This here's Joan and Bert Hey
Snack, y'all alright?
Oh, and you?
Must be that voice I heard from out here
Oh, he was beautiful God damn beautiful
voice Even through these walls Hmm Where y
'all from?
Just down the road And how far is that?
North Carolina Y'all clean?
Sir Well, we believe in equality and music
We just came here to play Spend some money
Have a good time Here, I'll show you
I picked for robbing clean Picked for
robbing clean I picked his head,
I picked his feet I would've picked his
body but it wouldn't fit to eat Oh,
I picked for robbing clean
Picked for robbing clean And
I'm dissatisfied Having a
family You thugs ain't mad
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Just a minute.
It's just about to get good.
I believe you.
But this here is a juke joint.
Blues music?
We got money and we're ready to spend it
with y'all.
Sounding damn near perfect and you're
saying we ain't welcome?
No, I'm saying you get down that road,
you get back into town.
Plenty of white barrel houses down there.
Oh, this is because we're...
All right.
How'd she get in?
She's here because she's family.
Family.
Can't we just, for one night, just all be
family?
You don't need to do that, sir.
We'll be on our way.
But we're going to walk really fast.
We'll be real slow.
Just in case y'all change your mind.
Y'all have a nice night.
They gave me the wheelies.
Yeah, well, Craig, it's that nighttime.
I'll do that to you.
Well, I'm just saying.
What if Hogan would have set us up?
I knew we should have killed that clown
motherfucker.
Sam, can you just give us a little space?
Just a little bit, please?
Thank you.
Now, slow down, Smoke.
I don't think they got nothing to do with
each other.
You think they bought company?
I doubt it.
But we got enough people on us if they
did.
Shit, we forgot the trunk.
Man, why you ain't gonna remind me?
Fool, I told you to remind me.
Y'all don't need the trunk.
There was just three of them.
Now, listen to me.
What if they just came to say?
And what if somebody spilled something on
them?
Or stepped on their shoe?
Look at they woman a bit too long.
We gonna have a bigger problem than just a
fight.
Sure will do.
Don't let them in.
Hey, Chef, you wanna talk?
Yeah.
I seen your performance down there.
You wrote that song.
Yeah.
I got a few of them.
Yeah, I can't thank you enough for this.
I mean, y'all the ones who put that guitar
in my hand.
Now this.
You got the talent, that's for certain.
But all this ain't no life for nobody.
I know plenty of musicians.
Ain't never met a happy one.
Yeah, it's cute now.
But it get old.
That rambling.
Sammy, you got something else in you.
What today's shuttle do?
I'm heading off on my own.
Where you going?
Maybe Chicago.
You heard of my bayou?
Where?
Right here in Mississippi.
Small town.
Found it by free slaves.
No crime.
And everything.
Black home.
That sound like a crap.
Yeah, well, I seen it.
One day our daddy beat Stack real bad.
So we get in our minds, it's time for us
to run away.
See, me, I wanted to go to the next
plantation over.
But Stack, he figured we'd get to Mount
Bayou.
So?
Got us a map.
Stole us a car.
And I got us there.
Why y'all ain't stay?
The mayor, he didn't want us.
Saying we was kids.
See, the thing is, that mayor knew who our
daddy was.
Knew he was an evil man.
Figured there was no way that he ain't
passed that evil down to us.
See, what I'm getting at, your daddy a
preacher, you can go and do that.
You like making music, make church music.
You want to leave, go on down Mount Bayou,
live with the proper black folks,
leave all this here improper shit to us.
I can't do that.
I mean, being with y'all today... Smoke,
I feel like I'm flying.
Yeah?
Well, you better enjoy the rest of the
night, because this is your last juke.
Look, come tomorrow, I'll find out about
you playing in one of these.
Boy, I'll kill you myself.
Well, I ain't going to Mount Bayou.
My daddy a Reverend, but I'm y'all cousin
too.
And a lot more people know the Smokestack
Twins than they know my daddy.
Look, I'm leaving that plantation just
like y'all did.
And if that's a problem for you,
kill me now.
1xBet has a huge choice of casino games.
1xBet, touch the wick tree.
What's wrong?
We have a packed house, but we underwater.
All the plantations down there paying with
credits.
All the plantations?
Yeah, seem that way.
What about them crackers?
What about them?
I can go feel them out before they're too
far gone.
Not gonna happen.
I can feel them out myself.
They'll tell me more than they'll tell
you.
And I can find out what they really have.
And what happens if they're from Little
Rock?
They ain't.
Let me go get this money for us.
I know y'all need it.
And what's that supposed to mean?
Irish beer, Italian wine.
You rob both sides.
Let them blame each other while you and
Smoke come down here and set up shop.
You gonna need every dime you can get when
they put two and two together.
But they won't.
They might.
Let me go talk to them and see about
putting something real on the two.
Come on.
All around
Will you go I see you go
Oh the summer time has
come And the trees
are sweetly blooming Will
I see you go
By a cruel and crystal fountain On it I
will All the flowers of the mountain Will
you go I see you go Are you looking for
some fresh air?
I just come to see if y'all was good
people.
Oh darling, that's so sweet of you.
So sweet.
We most surely are.
And y'all got money to spend?
Oh yeah.
Plenty of money.
You wanna see?
Yeah, I wanna see.
What type of money is this?
Solid gold kind, darling.
Yeah.
Where's this from?
It's from a different place and a
different time.
And it spins just the same.
You can have it.
But it's no good to you.
It's no good to her.
Mm-mm.
Well, what makes you say that?
Cause you're in some deep, deep pain that
money can't fix.
Am I right?
You came over here for fellowship and
love.
Fellowship and love.
My mother...
She just passed.
Oh, that's awful.
Just awful.
Losing a mother's a hurting feeling.
Mm-hmm.
I wish in my heart that we'd have met
sooner.
I would have liked to have saved her
mother from her fate.
I can still save you from yours.
Oh, now you must have me confused.
I'm sad is all, but I don't need no
saving.
Yes.
Yes, you do.
You all do.
I'm gonna head back now.
And I think y'all should too.
Back to wherever y'all came from.
Come on, Brad.
Man, what you done out there?
You gonna let me in?
Or just sit there blocking the door?
No.
Come on.
Come on in.
Man, it's hot in there, boy.
Hey, watch the door for me.
I got the pill.
Hold on, hold on.
Hey.
Where you coming from?
Boy, you ain't shit.
Watch the door.
Alas.
So what happened?
Hell yeah.
Boy, they want a drink of this or
something?
You sure?
Okay.
I don't want any shit.
Go out there and tell them to do
something.
Mm.
Oh, you scared?
You scared?
Nah.
It's just that you somebody else.
Uh huh.
So you rob chains and banks.
But you can't steal this pussy from a
knight.
Pick up that.
What the hell going on?
Come on.
This some bitch had loaded dice and been
wearing a sock!
Best you put that blade down.
Can't do that, twin.
Told him not to put his hands on me.
So you gonna cut me, too?
If I have to, I just wanna be allowed to
lead.
Come check his pockets.
Shit.
You took dirt out of my pants!
Don't it shine once more, that's what I
said.
Don't let it shine.
Y'all gonna take care of this fool.
Pale pale moon.
Pale pale pale moon.
Pale...
See?
Scream.
You want some?
Pale pale moon.
Pale pale...
I'm sorry.
Yeah, you're gonna need some stitches.
Go and get my brother.
Hey Slim!
You seen Stack?
Oh yeah, he's in the back.
He's about to strike.
You can go for it.
Hey Stack, Smoke is looking for you.
Shit!
Oh, he's busy, huh?
You gonna get him?
No.
Then why the hell not?
He was getting some lucky.
I don't give a fuck what he's doing.
I told you to go get him, didn't I?
I ain't doing that by myself.
Hey, where the hell is Korn Bray?
I was building you a new outhouse.
Nigga left to take a piss two and a half
days ago.
And he left you to watch the door.
You think I can't handle it?
Y'all get decent, I'm coming in.
I don't want you here playing around.
Fuck!
That's not what it looks like.
We gonna kill every last one of you.
Fuck you!
You are the real fun of the night.
What happened?
Where is she?
She left me.
I'm so scared.
I want you.
I'm so sorry.
Slim, keep everybody out.
Slim, who is shooting?
Are you going to bring the music back?
What the hell with the music, Slim?
Is Sammy in there?
Yes, Sammy is on the record.
The party is over.
No.
Yes, the party is over.
Who is she?
You are the man.
Go on.
Thank you.
We really appreciate you.
Go on.
Damn.
It's getting good.
Thank you.
See you soon.
We got us a problem, y'all.
I could have stopped it.
Don't do that.
I thought they was making love.
I thought...
Sammy, this is not your fault.
You start really dead.
Did she say anything?
She said we gonna kill all of you.
We?
She said we.
Smoke.
We gotta move his body.
Outside.
Just for now.
Don't touch him.
Nobody moved him.
You shot her and she kept running like
nothing happened.
This ain't we dealing with smoke.
Or worse, we gotta keep everybody inside
and the dead body out.
There ain't no dead body.
You're staying.
You're staying in here with me.
Don't know all that magic.
You got any magic to bring my brother
back?
Got a motive.
I told you we were back for him.
Please.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Let him.
Let him go.
We gotta go.
What?
We gotta get out of here.
Man, he's lost his brother.
Look, we came here to help him with the
party, not this.
We gotta go home, okay?
Lisa's waiting.
Yeah.
Okay?
Let's go home.
Yeah.
We'll get the car.
Alright.
I'll get the car.
Okay.
Yeah.
Watch over him.
Bam!
Smoke!
Where the hell you been at, man?
Huh?
To go see a man about a dog, like I told
you, you old drunk.
Turns out I need to take a shit,
too.
God dawg!
What happened to you, Smoke?
It's stagnation.
Nigga, what the fuck happened to you?
I'm sorry.
Alright, well, let me in so I can help.
Hold on.
What y'all doing?
Just step aside and let me on in,
now?
Why you need him to do that?
You being strong enough to push passes?
Well, that wouldn't be too polite now,
would it, Miss Annie?
I don't know why I'm talking to you
anyway.
Probably your fish sandwich messed up my
guts in the first place.
Using old stale grease.
I ain't never used stale grease,
and you know it.
Shut up, Annie.
Smoke.
Don't talk to him.
You talking to me right now.
Why you can't just walk your big ass up in
here without an invite, huh?
Go ahead.
Admit to it.
Admit to what?
That you dead.
That one of them white folks out there
killed you and you a hank now.
Smoke, you listening to this?
Yes.
Woman, this man showed me kindness.
Employed me.
Grabbed me out the field.
Now he say his brother been killed.
The man needs comfort.
Not you filling up his mind with that old
Louisiana Bayou bullshit you on.
Now we out here playing
games, telling ghost
stories, in place of doing
what we ought to do.
Cornbread.
Yeah.
At what is it we supposed to be doing?
Being kind to one another.
And being polite.
Now, we is one people.
And we shouldn't go in barging into other
folks' places uninvited, so...
We been in and out of here all day.
Ain't never need to invite them.
Yeah.
Something ain't that new.
Shit, Stack, what's my ride up here?
I'm supposed to walk back?
Ain't my problem.
Well, it be your own peoples.
Now, I thought you was better than that.
But you just like the white man.
Can I at least get my money?
Oh, you did such a bang up job.
Now you want to get paid for what you
ain't did?
Ain't nobody talking to you, you old
drunk.
Shut your mouth.
You shut the fuck up.
Don't give me shit, Smoke.
Don't give me nothing.
Careful.
Smoke!
Oh, my.
I'm all right.
I don't know.
Hey.
You ever smell anything?
No.
I think I shot myself.
Oh, my God.
Why the hell you get up back?
I don't know.
I've been thinking this heat.
Smoke... Smoke!
Smoke.
Stay.
N***a, that's you?
Nah, fool.
It's Jim Crow.
N***a, of course it's me.
Open the door.
Huh?
Stay.
How you feeling?
Boy, you lost a lot of blood.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, uh...
It was scary, huh?
I'm doing much better now.
I swear.
On Mama Grace.
I thought you said he was dead.
He was.
I checked his pulse.
Then what the fuck is he doing talking to
us?
But this is good, right?
Means he's okay.
Smoke...
That ain't your brother.
You gonna let her get in between us again?
What we been through.
German trenches, n***a.
Chicago gangways.
Come on, man.
Open the door.
It's me.
Y'all think you're Sweet Lock and a pimp
in a closet, huh?
You know I don't like this shit,
man.
Please, smoke.
Let me out of this room.
Smoke, please.
Annie, give me the key.
It's not...
Sam, come here.
What was in the jar?
Pickled garlic.
These ain't heaps.
They're vampires.
Bo's out there.
We gotta go get him.
I'm the one who sent him out there.
We can't let you do that.
He needs my help.
Bo know how to handle himself.
Probably got in that car and got someplace
safe.
Y'all ain't gonna keep me from my husband.
Grace, we trying to keep you alive right
now.
We just gotta hold up till sunrise.
Okay?
Now we need...
garlic...
...wood...
...silver... ...holy water.
Wait.
How could it move and sound like static?
If it ain't static.
I only ever heard stories.
I ain't never come across them myself.
What stories you heard?
How haints work.
They switch places with the soul of a man.
But vampires is different.
Maybe the worst kind.
The soul gets stuck in the body.
Can't rejoin the ancestors.
Cursed to live here with all this hate.
Can't even feel the warmth of a sunrise.
Okay then.
Can we bring him back?
The best thing we can do for him is free
his spirit from this curse.
How the hell do we do that?
Sunlight.
That wouldn't stake to the heart.
He'll heal, ain't he?
I kept that boy safe all these years.
All over this world.
What a night.
It was cause of me.
My daddy told me.
Said the devil was coming on account of my
music.
You know how that gal once?
The vampire?
He was light-skinned, too.
That gal bit me everywhere above my neck.
Sammy.
You don't worry about a thing,
yeah?
The devil done came for me plenty of
times.
If he come knocking tonight, I'm gonna
kill him.
He gonna have to go through his old
friend, Delta Slim, before he get to you.
That go for everybody in here.
If I get bit by one of them, promise me
right now that you'll free me before I turn.
What you mean free you?
I got somebody on the other side waiting
for me.
They waiting on you, too.
You understand?
I don't give a what that shit say.
I'm gonna make sure you get home safe.
Sammy!
Smoke!
Who did this?
Was it Stag or Mary?
No.
They ran straight out.
You saw them?
Who bit him then?
We gotta get him out before he wakes up.
They playing music.
I caught a stone black for two banished
ghosts and goblins.
A brand new pair of brogues to rattle over
the bogs and frighten all the dogs.
Let's get back inside.
Come on.
On the rocky road to Dublin.
One, two, three, four, five.
While in the merry month of Christmas.
Mary took me home.
I started left the girls of June.
We're nearly brokenhearted.
Saluted father dear.
Kissed me darling.
Other drank a pint of beer.
My grief and tears to smother.
Then off to reap the corn.
Leave where I was born.
Got a stone black gone to banish ghosts.
And goblins brand new pair of brogues
rattling over the bogs.
Frightened all the dogs on the rocky road
to Dublin.
One, two, three, four, five.
Up the hair and turn her down the rocky
road.
And all the way to Dublin.
Whack-a-lolly-da.
From there I got to Weaver Street.
On Saturday we landed on the...
We all gonna eat this clove of garlic.
I don't much like the taste of it.
Ain't no one saying you gotta like it.
We just gotta figure out if any of us left
is one of them.
Yum.
You don't get none of the pickle ones?
This is ridiculous.
Smoke, put the gun down.
Shut up.
Beat or I'll shoot.
Put the gun down, Smoke.
She ain't no damn vampire.
How the hell you know that?
Just eat the damn garlic, girl.
Smoke!
Trying to keep you alive, boy.
You ain't to question me.
You an evil man.
No wonder the devil come for us.
You ain't gotta point no gun at me.
Slim, what's going on, man?
Talk to me, Slim.
Slim?
What's going on, Slim?
I drank too much.
That goddamn beer from Chicago.
My nerves all fucked up.
I'm fine.
See?
You sure that was blood?
Smoke, let me in, man.
Smoke, let me in.
Smoke, I swear I paid my time,
man.
That's what this about.
Smoke.
Whatever you need, man.
Smoke!
Some weird shit going on out here,
Smoke.
I know you here, Smoke.
Smoke, let me in.
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh, shit.
Come on, bitch.
Close the door.
Come on.
Wait!
Come on, baby.
Come on outside.
I got the car started.
Let's go.
What is it, Grace?
He's killing him.
Oh, you talking about that?
I don't know about cornbread.
I'm just a little hungry, that's all.
Let's go.
Come on.
Come on and go.
I got the car all warmed up.
Or...
You can let me back in there.
I'll come in and we can grab our things
and head home.
Don't listen to him.
Grace, we gonna find a way out of this,
I promise.
I am.
Your way out.
This world already left you for dead.
Won't let you build.
Won't let you fellowship.
We will do just that.
Together.
Forever.
It's better this way, baby.
So why don't you go ahead and invite us
in.
You should listen to him, Grace.
Or listen to me.
Because I know everything he knows now.
And I want you to let us in there.
Or we gonna go to the grocery store.
We gonna pay little Lisa a visit.
No!
Don't you fucking dare!
I know everything now.
Let us in.
No no no, please.
I'm going.
You're the devil.
It's you.
Sammy!
Sammy Sammy Sammy.
Travelling Travelling
Travelling I don't want
to be I don't know where
in the world I've been.
Hey, y'all give him to me now.
Just give me a little Sammy.
We'll let y'all live.
Hey, Woozy.
I'm gonna tell you something.
You can't have him.
He belongs to us.
He belongs with us.
You can't have him.
And I ain't gonna let that happen.
You can't save him.
Smoke no more than you could save your
brother.
You ain't safe here.
No matter how many guns or how much money,
they gonna take it from you when they want.
You built something here tonight and it
was beautiful.
But it was built on a lie.
Hogwood.
He's the grand dragon of the Ku Klux Klan.
That's his motherfuckin' nephew.
They was always gonna kill you.
I just happened to see him.
He show up at the right place at the right
time.
He tellin' the truth, Smoke.
I can see his memories.
This wasn't no juke joint.
No club.
This here is a slaughterhouse.
It's a goddamn killin' floor.
Why can't y'all just go?
Cause we not leavin' without y'all.
We family.
Ain't that right?
I know it sound crazy, but...
after we kill y'all...
we gonna have heaven right here on Earth.
Oh.
How you there?
Come on.
Welcome.
Look away.
Smoke.
That ain't your brother.
Fuck you, nigga.
It is me.
Elias Small.
And I'm talkin' to my big brother right
now, Slim.
So I'ma kindly ask you to shut the fuck
up.
I'ma kindly ask you to shut the fuck up.
We ain't never gonna be free.
We been runnin' around everywhere lookin'
for freedom.
You know damn well you was never gonna
find it.
Until this.
This is the way.
Together.
Forever.
And I ain't doin' this shit without you.
There is no me without you.
What's it gonna be?
No.
Close the door.
No vision.
He said he was gonna take our daughter.
You can't believe him.
He was just trynna get you to let him in.
He ain't threaten your children!
We just gotta stay through the night.
And what?
Let him kill my family?
Kill the whole town?
Turn everybody to monsters?
We got to stop them, Smoke.
We got to get them before they get away.
Rachel, slow down.
Give me a second to think.
What?
Ain't you a soldier?
Didn't you just shoot two men for touching
your truck?
They killed your brother.
Made Stack one of them.
My beau.
Said they was going to kill you.
If now ain't go time, then I don't know
what is.
We supposed to wait the night while they
take more of her loved ones?
Make them demons?
You don't look like they leaving,
Gracie.
Shut your drunk ass up, Slim.
I ain't drunk right now.
You need to watch your mouth, woman.
What you doing?
Stop that.
Come on.
Y'all hear that?
It's the song they was singing.
I pick for I'll be clean.
And I'll be satisfied, having family.
When
I pick for I'll be clean.
When I
pick for I'll be clean.
No, let go of me!
We'll kill all of them.
Let go!
We got to fight.
We've got to think honestly.
We've got to fight.
Come on!
Come on, Eddie, you mother...
You promised me.
I think so.
I love you.
Eddie!
No!
Smoke, we've got to get the boy at the
back so he's not here.
Come on.
Smoke, come on now.
Up the steps.
Go ahead.
Is that it?
Is that what I told you?
Go!
Now go!
You're still nasty.
Hey.
Last call I've never seen.
Get out of here!
Sammy!
Where are you going?
What the fuck is wrong with you,
man?
I want your stories.
And I want your songs.
And you don't have mine.
Our father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done,
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread,
and forgive us our trespasses,
and forgive those who trespass against us.
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
Oh my.
Long ago, the man who stole my father's
land forced these words upon us.
Oh, I hated those men.
But the words still bring me comfort.
Hey!
Throw your weapons!
Throw them!
Oh, boy.
Those men lied to themselves and lied to
us.
They told stories of a god above and a
devil below.
And lies of a dominion of man over beasts
and earth.
Jesus.
We are earth and beast and god.
We are woman and man.
We are connected.
You and I.
To everything.
Shit!
You will taste the sweet pain of death.
We will make beautiful music together.
Go home.
And bury that fucking guitar.
I can't.
It's Charlie Page.
What?
What he told you that?
What's that?
He said y'all wanted over.
Lion song, bitch.
That's our daddy guitar.
Be strong.
Hear me?
I got some business to handle.
Be strong.
Yeah?
Yeah.
And if we see you or any one of your clan
buddies cross our property line,
we gonna kill them right where they stand.
Okay then.
You fucking perv.
Club juke, huh?
Grand opening, grand closing.
Let's do it.
Open it up.
Come on son.
It's okay.
My son has felt the call of sin.
You see where that gets you?
Door's locked.
Try the front.
This one is too.
But the good Lord calls upon us to be
fishers of men who sin and show them the way.
And before this congregation believe those
sinning ways where they lie.
I want you to promise right now.
Drop the guitar, Sam.
In the name of God.
My
brother will serve you.
My son has returned.
I know some of you.
You hear the call of the devil trying to
steal you away.
Slick-talking men and loose women.
You can let them call and not answer.
You tell them.
My heart.
My body.
My voice.
My soul.
You got a cigarette?
You go to hell, nigger.
You put that cig out, you can hold her.
I don't want any smoke to get on her.
Hey, listen.
I got money.
Huh?
No.
Probably here.
Let it go, Sammy.
Drop the guitar.
Put it down.
Hey, boss.
I got two out there.
I told them to close, but they offered a
couple hundred bucks.
That okay with you?
That don't bother me none.
Come on in.
Sammy!
I'll have whatever the old man have me.
When I saw him kill Andy...
I knew I had to get Mary out of there.
She hid in the woods.
As for me...
Sorry I couldn't keep you safe.
Don't be sorry.
You always be.
I guess I was the one person he just
couldn't kill.
He made me promise to stay away from you.
Let you live out your life.
You know, we got every single one of your
records.
I don't like that electric shit as much as
the real.
Yeah.
I miss the real.
Records from back then sound like a pile
of dog shit.
How about it, Sammy?
You still got the real in you.
Traveling...
I don't know why in the hell...
Take care, little Sammy.
You know something?
Maybe once a week... I wake
up every morning... Paralyzed.
Relive it that night.
But before the sun went down...
I think that was the best day of my life.
Was it like that for you?
No doubt about it.
Last time I seen my brother...
I love you.
Last time I seen the sun...
and just for a few hours...
it was free.